Feel like trying something new for dinner?
Tu veux tenter un nouveau resto ?
Maybe Indian? Tex-Mex?
Indien ? Tex-mex ?
Ever wonder how humans would be different if they evolved...
Tu t'es déjà demandé comment l'Homme serait
...from lizards instead of mammals?
s'il avait évolué à partir du lézard ?
LEONARD: Okay, let's talk about that.
D'accord, changeons de sujet.
As you know, lizards, cold-blooded animals...
Animaux à sang froid, les lézards sont incapables
...lack the ability to sense temperature.
de percevoir les températures,
But they do move more sluggishly when it's cold.
mais se meuvent plus lentement par temps froid.
So lizard weathermen would say things like:
Les présentateurs météo diraient donc :
"Bring a sweater, it's slow outside."
"Couvrez-vous bien, il fera lent demain."
I love my mind.
J‘adore mon esprit.
We all do. Now, how about dinner?
Comme nous tous. Et pour le diner ?
Oh, I would assume we'd enjoy insects or smaller lizards.
Nous nous régalerions sans doute d'insectes ou de petits lézards.
We could also pull each other's tails off and grill them. They'll just grow back.
Nous pourrions aussi manger un bout de notre queue. Elle repousserait.
My life-size card board Mr. Spock is here.
Ma silhouette en carton de M. Spock est arrivée !
I know he wouldn't care for an outburst of human emotion...
Je sais qu'il n‘a cure des émotions humaines,
...but, oh, goodie, oh, goodie, oh, goodie.
mais chouette, chouette, chouette!
Commander Spock requesting permission to be unfolded.
Ici le capitaine Spock, demandons permission d‘être déballé.
-Excuse me. -Permission granted, commander.
- Excuse-moi. - Permission accordée.
--which is why the more intelligent the monkey, the more feces they fling.
Donc, plus le singe est intelligent, plus il lance de déjections.
Excuse me, Amy. Uh, Penny, do you have plans for dinner?
Excuse-moi, Amy. Penny, tu fais quoi ce soir ?
-You guys going somewhere? -No,just you and me.
- Vous sortez ? - J'aimerais dîner avec toi.
You mean, like a date?
Entre copains ?
Not like a date, a date.
En tête-à-tête.
Okay. Sure.
Euh... d‘accord.
Oh, no. They sent the wrong Spock.
Oh, non ! Ils se sont trompés de Spock.
Live long and suck it, Zachary Quinto.
Longue vie et dégage, Zachary Quinto !
This is so exciting. If Leonard and Penny get back together...
C‘est si excitant. S‘ils se remettent ensemble,
...Howard and I can go on double dates with them.
on aura un autre couple avec lequel sortir.
How come you never invite Sheldon and me on a double date?
Sheldon et moi sommes un couple.
How's it going in there, Penny?
Tu t'en sors, Penny ?
PENNY: Just a sec.
Une seconde !
Too much?
C‘est trop ?
-Yes. -No.
-Oui. - Non.
Okay. Just hang on.
D‘accord. Je reviens.
You just can't handle her raw sexuality, can you?
Tu n‘arrives vraiment pas a accepter sa sexualité prononcée.
When did you and Leonard break up?
Quand avez-vous rompu ?
PENNY: Uh, about two years ago.
Il y a deux ans.
Why do you think he asked you out again?
Pourquoi t'invite—HI, d‘après toi ?
PENNY: I don't know. -Maybe he's dying.
- Va savoir. - Il va peut-être mourir.
That would be so romantic.
Ce serait trop romantique.
PENNY: He's not dying.
Il ne va pas mourir.
Too bad.
Dommage.
If he were, she could throw him in bed and ride him right up until he flatlines.
Elle aurait pu le chevaucher jusqu‘à ce que son cœur lâche.
How about this?
Etça?
-Maybe. -Come on.
- Faut voir. - Pitié !
Yeah, okay, no.
Non. D‘accord.
Do you think you'll sleep with him tonight?
Vous allez coucher ensemble ?
PENNY: Absolutely not. We're just gonna have dinner and, you know, see how it goes.
Sûrement pas. On va dîner et laisser faire les choses.
If he were dying, would you sleep with him?
S'il était mourant, tu le ferais ?
PENNY: What? -Assuming he were dying...
- Quoi ? - En supposant
...of something that couldn't be sexually transmitted.
qu'il se meure d‘une chose non sexuellement transmissible.
You know, like a spear wound to the head.
Comme une lance dans la tête.
PENNY: Okay, he is not dying.
Il n‘est pas mourant.
How do you know? Are you a doctor?
Comment tu le sais ? Tu es médecin ?
You can make-believe though.
Mais tu peux faire semblant.
Sometimes Howard and l pretend that his arrhythmia is acting up...
Avec Howard, on imagine parfois qu'il tachycarde
...and I'm a sexy cardiologist...
et que je suis une cardiologue,
...and the naughty part is I'm not in his HMO network.
àla fois non conventionnée et non conventionnelle.
Screw it. I'm not gonna make a big deal out of this. It's just dinner.
Zut. J‘arrête de me prendre la tête. Ce n‘est qu'un dîner.
With a dead man. Rawr.
Avec un mourant.
Amy, stop it.
Amy, arrête.
Oh, God, I'm so nervous.
Je suis hyper nerveuse.
Relax. You know Leonard's always been crazy about you. It's gonna be great.
Pourquoi ? Leonard est fou de toi. Vous allez vous amuser.
We've finally gotten to a place where we can hang out without it being weird.
Ça redevient enfin normal entre nous alors que se passera—HI
-If something goes wrong, then what? -lt'll just be Sheldon and me...
- si c‘est un fiasco ? - Il n‘y aura plus que Sheldon et moi
...going on a double date with Howard and Bernadette.
pour sortir avec Howard et Bernadette.
Sure. We'd love that.
Oui. Avec grand plaisir.
Change your clothes, we got a lot riding on this.
Change-toi. On joue gros, ce soir.
I want to build a road, but I need wood.
Je veux construire une route, maisj'ai un probléme de rondin.
Do either of you fellows have wood?
Qui est bien pourvu a ce niveau-là ?
I don't understand the laughter.
Qu‘est—ce qui vous fait rire ?
The object of Settlers of Catan is to build roads and settlements...
Le but de ce jeu est de bâtir des colonies.
...to do so requires wood. Now, I have sheep, I need wood.
J'ai des moutons, mais je dois mettre la main sur des rondins.
Who has wood for my sheep?
Avez-vous de quoi me satisfaire ?
Okay. How do I look?
De quoi j'ai l‘air ?
More to the point, why are you doing this?
Pourquoi tu fais ça ?
-What are you talking about? -You forget what Penny did to you?
- Comment ça ? - Tu as oublié ce qu'elle t‘a fait ?
It took you two years and defiling my sister to turn that frown upside down.
Il t‘a fallu deux ans et déshonorer ma sœur pour l'oublier.
I didn't defile your sister, we had a relationship.
Je ne l'ai pas déshonorée, nous sortions ensemble.
I heard you call her Brown Sugar.
Tu l'appelais mon sucre brun.
In my book that's defilement.
Chez moi, c‘est déshonorant.
-You wanna know my opinion? -Oh, boy, do I.
- Tu veux mon avis ? - Oh la la, oui alors!
Sarcasm?
Sarcasme ?
All right, then.
Trés bien.
The reason you're fixated on a good-natured simpleton like Penny...
Tu fais une fixation sur notre simple et gentille Penny
...is that she's the exact opposite of your first romantic attachment...
parce qu'elle est l'exacte opposée de ton premier amour.
...your brilliant, yet intimidating, mother.
Ta brillante et intimidante mère.
Where on earth did you get that from?
Où es-tu allé pêcher ça ?
It's in her book Needy Baby, Greedy Baby.
Dans son livre, Bébé dépendant, bébé gourmand.
That doesn't make it true.
Ce n‘est pas vrai pour autant.
It's called non-fiction for a reason, Leonard.
Ça ne s‘appelle pas ”non-fiction" pour rien.
See you later.
A plus tard.
If they make a movie version of that book...
Si on en faisait film, vous savez
...you know who should play Leonard's mother? Sandra Bullock.
qui devraitjouer sa mère ? Sandra Bullock.
-Why? -Because she's great in everything.
- Pourquoi ? - Parce qu'elle est merveilleuse.
Now, where were we? Oh, yes. Does anyone have any wood?
Où en étions-nous ? Ah oui, mon probléme de rondin.
Come on. I just want wood. Why are you making it so hard?
Allez, passez—moi vos rondins. C‘est suffisamment dur comme ça.
So do they have a name for a first date with someone you used to go outwith?
Le fait de ressortir pour la 1re fois avec un ex a un nom, tu crois ?
That's a good question. How about "awkward"?
Bonne question. Que dis-tu de ”gênant" ?
-Yeah, that sounds right. -Yeah? Heh, heh.
- Pas mal. - N'est-ce pas ?
How about if we pretend we're actually on a first date? See how that goes.
Pourquoi ne pas imaginer qu'il s'agit réellement d'un 1er rencard ?
Okay.
D‘accord.
So, Polly, tell me about yourself.
Parle—moi un peu de toi, Polly.
Okay, let's see. I'm from Nebraska, and ever since I was a little girl...
Je Viens du Nebraska et, toute petite déjà,
...I dreamed of moving to LA. and becoming a movie star.
je rêvais de m‘installer à LA. et de devenir une star.
Anyway, after four years of acting lessons and waiting tables...
Au final, je suis serveuse, j'ai tourné une pub
...l've done a hemorrhoid commercial...
pour un anti—hémorroïdes
...and a production of Anne Frank above a bowling alley.
etj'ai joué Anne Frank dans un bowling.
So you know, dreams do come true.
Preuve qu'on peut réaliser ses rêves.
-Your turn. -Uh, let's see. Ahem. Uh....
- A toi. - Voyons voir.
I am an experimental physicist at Caltech.
Je suis chercheur en physique au Caltech.
Most of my research is with high-powered lasers, and--
J'étudie les lasers haute puissance et…
Oh, I've just gotten a big government grant...
Le gouvernement m‘a alloué des fonds
...to see if they can be used to knock out incoming ballistic missiles.
pour voir s‘ils ne pourraient pas neutraliser des missiles.
-Wow. Can they? -Oh, God, no.
- C‘est le cas ? - Grands dieux, non.
But the money's pretty good.
Mais c‘est bien payé.
And I used the equipment to make my own Bat-Signal.
Etj'ai de quoi créer mon propre bat—signal.
Bat-Signal? What are you, some kind of nerd?
Un hat—signal ? Serais-tu un ringard ?
Not some kind of nerd, lam the king of nerds.
Pas un ringard. Le roi des ringards.
-What does that mean? -It means if anyone displeases me...
- Qu‘est—ce que ça veut dire ? - Que si tu me contraries,
...I don't help them set up their printer.
tu configureras ton imprimante toute seule.
You are so funny.
Tu me fais rire.
Good. Remember that when I take my shirt off.
Tant mieux. Souviens-t'en quand j‘enléverai ma chemise.
-This is nice. I'm so glad we did this. -Me too.
- Je passe une trés bonne soirée. - Pareil.
So, what do you think, are we gonna get back together?
Alors, tu veux qu'on se remette ensemble ?
Whoa, not so fast.
Tout doux.
I'm sorry, what did I say?
Qu‘est—ce que j'ai dit ?
Leonard, you know I will always have feelings for you--
Leonard, tu sais que je t‘aime...
-Oh, God. -What?
- C‘est pas vrai. - Quoi ?
You said "always." You'll always have feelings for me.
Tu as dit : "Tu sais que je t'aime."
-So? -That sounds like something you'd say...
- Et alors ? - C‘est ce qu'on dit
...if you didn't want a relationship with someone.
quand on ne veut pas sortir avec quelqu‘un.
"This isn't working out, but I'll always have feelings for you."
"Tu sais que je t‘aime, mais ça ne marcherajamais."
"I'm sorry I slept with your best friend,
”J‘ai couché avec ton meilleur ami, mais tu sais que je t'aime."
"Here's the thing, Lisa, I'm into dudes now...
"Ecoute, Lisa. Tu sais que je t‘aime,
...but I'll always have feelings for you."
mais je préfère les mecs."
-How would you say it? -l have feelings for you.
- Que faut-il dire ? - Je t‘aime.
-Same thing. -No, it's not. "Always" made it worse.
- C‘est pareil. - Non. Le “tu sais" gâche tout.
-You're over-thinking this. -No, I'm not.
- Tu suranalyses les choses. - Non.
-You always over-think things. -There you go. "Always" made it worse.
- Tu fais toujours ça et tu le sais. - Là aussi, ça gâche tout.
See, this is where everything goes wrong, when we talk.
C‘est ça notre problème, on ne devrait pas parler.
Well, I don't know how you have a relationship without talking.
Comment peut-on sortir avec quelqu'un sans lui parler ?
I went out with T.J. for eight months. We never talked.
Je suis sortie avec un T.J. pendant huit mois
To this day, I don't even know what T.J. stands for.
etje ne sais toujours pas ce que T.J. veut dire.
Wait, if you guys didn't talk--? Never mind, stupid question.
Qu‘est—ce que vous... Laisse tomber. Question stupide.
And now that l have some wood...
Mon problème de rondins étant résolu,
...l'm going to begin the erection of my settlement.
je peux procéder à l'érection de ma colonie.
He's got to be doing this on purpose.
Il en fait exprès, c‘est pas possible.
Ooh, eight-thirty. You and Penny decide to go out and paint the town beige?
20h30 ? Une telle bringue n‘est plus de votre âge.
You're 30 years old and you live with your mother.
Tu as 30 ans et tu vis chez ta mère.
I guess it didn't go well.
Mauvaise soirée.
We don't know that. Not to a certainty.
Ca, nous n'en savons rien.
All we know is that Leonard is home.
Nous savons seulement que Leonard est rentré.
How about now?
Et la?
Again, not enough evidence. For all we know, he's being murdered.
Ça ne prouve toujours rien. Il peut aussi bien se faire trucider.
Now, back to our game.
Bien, reprenons.
You were in the middle of an erection.
Tu étais en pleine érection.
Oh, of course. It's right here in my hand.
Exact ! C‘était dans ma main.
What does she want from me now?
Qu‘est—ce qu'elle me veut ?
-What's up? -Do not over-think this.
- Quoi ? - Ne suranalyse pas.
-I don't understand-- -Bup, bup, bup.
Je ne comprends pas...
-Okay, but earlier it seemed like-- -No talking.
- Tout a l'heure, tu... - On se tait.
LEONARD: Even during? Because sometimes I have questions.
Tout du long ? Parce qu'il m'arrive d‘avoir des questions.
Well, that was fun.
C‘était très sympa.
Yeah. Except for when I got the foot cramp.
Oui. Sauf Ia crampe au pied.
You hung in there though.
Mais tu as tenu bon.
There was a lot at stake.
Il y avait beaucoup en jeu.
So, what do you wanna do now?
Et maintenant ?
Well, I wanna go get my asthma inhaler, but it might ruin the moment.
J'irais bien chercher mon inhalateur, mais ça casserait l‘ambiance.
So help me out, here. How does a miserable date end in sex?
Comment est-on passés d'un rencard raté a des galipettes ?
I don't know, it's complicated.
Je ne sais pas. C‘est compliqué.
I'm pretty smart guy, and right now my brain has dibs on the blood supply...
Mon cerveau est a nouveau prioritaire sur l'afflux sanguin,
...so give it a go.
alors dis toujours.
Okay. It's just--
D‘accord. C'est...
At that restaurant when you said you wanted us to be together again...
Quand tu as proposé qu'on se remette ensemble,
...it got very real, very fast and l panicked.
ça m‘a prise au dépourvu etj'ai paniqué.
Why? What are you afraid of?
Pourquoi ? De quoi as-tu peur ?
Well, what if we do go out and I do something stupid and dump you again?
De refaire un truc stupide et de te larguer une 2e fois.
What ifl dump you?
Je pourrais aussi bien te larguer.
Come on, be serious.
Sois sérieux une seconde.
Well, how about if we don't think about this as a relationship?
Rien ne nous oblige à nous considérer comme un couple.
It could be more like a new version of software.
Revisitons notre relation.
Penny and Leonard 2.0.
Penny et Leonard 2.0.
We can test it internally, shake out the bugs...
Testons-la, éliminons les anomalies
...and if we both feel it's solid, then we'll roll it out to the public.
et, si ça nous semble solide, commercialisons-la.
We don't tell people we're back together?
On ne dit rien aux autres ?
Exactly. We pretend like our date went badly.
Agissons comme si la soirée s‘était mal passée.
Well, we don't really have to pretend.
Ça ne sera pas bien difficile.
And we let them think that we decided to just be friends...
Faisons-leur croire qu'on a décidé d‘être amis
...and that everything's cool.
et que tout va bien.
Okay. Great.
D‘accord.
Hey, ljust remembered. I still got one of your inhalers.
Je Viens de me rappeler. J'ai encore un de tes inhalateurs.
I can't believe you kept this.
Tu as gardé ça ?
l was gonna throw it away, but I just couldn't.
Je n'ai jamais pu lejeter.
That is so sweet.
Je suis touché.
In 25 to 30 minutes I'm gonna show you how much this means to me.
Et dans 25 a 30 minutes, je te montrerai a quel point.
-Leonard? -Yeah, h i.
- Leonard ? - Salut.
How's it going?
Çava?
Can't complain, thanks for asking.
Je n'ai pas a me plaindre, merci.
What were you doing out at 3:00 in the morning?
Que fais-tu debout à 3 h du matin ?
Well-- What are you doing up?
Euh... Et toi ?
l was using the bathroom.
J‘étais aux toilettes.
Yeah,well, so was I.
Eh bien, pareil.
Really? I didn't see you in there.
Vraiment ? Je ne t'ai pas vu.
Obviously.
Normal.
When I saw that you were in ours, I went and used another one.
Quand j'ai vu que c‘était occupé, je suis allé en utiliser d‘autres.
Where?
Lesquelles ?
Uh, the gas station across the street.
Celles de Ia station-service, en bas.
-In your pajamas? -Yes.
- En pyjamas ? - Oui.
Without shoes?
Et en chaussettes ?
Yes.
Oui.
On a cold winter's night?
Par une froide nuit d‘hiver ?
That seems unlikely. Did you bring your asthma inhaler?
Voilà qui est inhabituel. Avais-tu pris ton inhalateur ?
Well, then I guess it's plausible.
C‘est plus vraisemblable.
-Hang on a second, mister. -What?
- Une petite minute,jeune homme. - Quoi ?
After you used the facilities at the gas station, did you make a purchase?
Après avoir utilisé les toilettes, as-tu acheté quelque chose ?
What?
Quoi ?
It's customary when using the restroom at a retail establishment...
Dans ce genre de situations, il est de coutume pour l'usager
...to make a small purchase. Did you?
d‘effectuer un petit achat. Est-ce le cas ?
Here's $2.
Voilà 2 $.
Go buy some beefjerky.
Va acheter des chewing-gums.
I don't want beefjerky.
J'ai pas envie de chewing-gums.
It's not about you.
La n‘est pas la question.
It's about a poor immigrant from Pakistan...
Il s'agit de soutenir un pauvre Pakistanais
...trying to make his way in America by working the graveyard shift...
qui s‘efforce de s'en sortir en travaillant de nuit
...at the Colorado Boulevard Chevron.
àla station Chevron de Colorado Bd.
Fine.
Bon, d‘accord.
Needy baby, greedy baby, indeed.
Bébé dépendant, bébé gourmand, tu l'as dit.
Leonard will be here in a moment.
Leonard ne va pas tarder.
He's looking for a different parking space.
Il change de place de parking.
-Why? -We were next to a car with an...
- Pourquoi ? - La voiture voisine avait
..."ask me about my grandchildren" bumper sticker...
un autocollant "Demandez-moi comment vont
...and l was afraid if we ran into them on the way out, I'd be obligated to do so.
mes petits—enfants". Je ne voulais pas avoir ale faire.
I'm so disappointed it didn't work with him and Penny.
Je regrette que ça n‘ait pas marché avec Penny.
Me too. Out of deference to them, let's not flaunt our happy relationship.
Oui. Par respect pour eux, évitons de faire étalage de notre bonheur.
You have a keen insight into the human heart, Amy Farrah Fowler.
Amy Farrah Fowler, vous êtes une femme très perspicace.
We are next to a Subaru with a Gore-Lieberman bumper sticker.
La Subaru d'à côté arbore un autocollant Gore Lieberman.
Well, I doubt they'd wanna talk about that, so we're fine.
Je doute que le propriétaire veuille en parler. Parfait.
I'm surprised to see you here after it went so badly with Penny.
Je suis surpris que tu sois la après l‘autre soir.
Well, hey, we're grown-ups. We can still be friends.
Penny et moi sommes adultes. On peut être amis.
Boy, I don't know if I could be friends with Howie if we broke up.
Je ne crois pas que je pourrais être amie avec Howie.
-Why not? -l'm a very vengeful person.
- Pourquoi ? - Je suis une femme très rancuniére.
-Really? -With access to weaponized smallpox.
- Ah bon ? - Qui a accès a de nombreux virus.
Let me get you some water. You need menus, or you know what you want?
Voilà un peu d'eau. Vous savez ce que vous voulez ?
Leonard knows what he wants, but it looks like he's not gonna get it from you.
Leonard a bien une petite idée, mais il peut faire une croix dessus.
-Howard. -No, that's okay, Bernadette.
- Howard. - Ce n‘est rien, Bernadette.
Sometimes these things just don't work out.
Ces choses-là ne se commandent pas.
Yeah. It's all good. We'll always have feelings for each other.
Oui. Tout baigne. Elle sait que je l‘aime.
See? She knew what "always" meant.
Elle comprend, elie.
Wow, you're like a dog with a bone, aren't you?
Tu vas nous remettre ça sur le tapis ?
-l'm just making a point. -Is the point you don't know...
- J'illustre un point de vue. - Quand apprendras-tu
-...when to let something go? -People, people, please.
- à lâcher l‘affaire ? - S'il vous plaît.
Before you say something you both regret...
Avant que les choses ne dégénérent,
...l'd like to place my order.
j'aimerais commander.
Yeah, hang on, Sheldon. You know why we can't be together?
Une seconde. Voilà pourquoi ça ne peut pas marcher.
-Because you always have to be right. -That is not true.
- Tu n'as jamais tort. - C‘est faux.
I gotta go with Leonard on this. He is wrong more than anyone I know.
Je suis d'accord avec lui. Il a constamment tort.
You know what, I just realized I'm on a break. I'll get someone else.
C‘est l‘heure de ma pause. Je vous envoie quelqu'un d'autre.
Promise me when our new waitress comes over...
Quand l‘autre serveuse arrivera,
...you will not start a complicated, on-again, off-again relationship with her.
promets—moi de ne pas entamer de relation compliquée avec elle.
Because I'm very, very hungry.
Je meurs de faim.
Unbelievable.
C‘est pas croyable.
Mind explaining why you were being a jerk at the restaurant?
Pourquoi as-tu été aussi désagréable au resto ?
l was trying to act like we weren't seeing each other. That was the plan.
On devait faire comme s'il n‘y avait rien entre nous.
The plan was to tell people we decided to stay friends.
Non, on devait se faire passer pour des amis.
But that's a little hard to do when you're always being such a toolbag.
Ce qui n‘est pas évident si tu te comportes en gros nul !
I don't have to stand here and take this crap.
Je n'ai pas à supporter ça.
Where do you think you're going?
Où est-ce que tu vas ?
Isn't sex after fighting kind of what we do now?
Je croyais qu'on terminait nos disputes au lit!
Yeah, kind of, yeah.
Tu as raison.
-What are we doing? -What do you mean?
- Que fait-on exactement ? - Comment ça ?
Every scenario I play out for you and me ends badly.
Je n'arrive pas à imaginer d‘issue positive.
Because you over-think everything.
Parce que tu suranalyses.
SHELDON: Leonard, are you listening to me?
Leonard, tu m'écoutes ?
-What? Yeah. -This is a disaster.
- Quoi ? Oui. - C‘est une catastrophe.
l distinctly ordered the Leonard Nimoy Mr. Spock cardboard standee.
J'ai pourtant bien précisé Leonard Nimroy sur ma commande.
Why would I feel safer with Zachary Quinto at the foot of my bed?
Pourquoi me sentirais-je plus en sécurité avec Zachary Quinto ?
I don't know. He was pretty badass on Heroes.
Je ne sais pas. Il était plutôt cool dans Heroes.
You're right. I'll give him a shot.
Tu as raison. Je vais lui donner une chance.
Hang on.
Je reviens.
-Penny, you have plans for dinner? -You guys going somewhere?
- Penny, tu fais quoi ce soir ? - Vous sortez ?
No, I mean just you and me.
J'aimerais dîner avec toi.
Have you thought this through?
Tu y as bien réfléchi ?
Yes. And I think we should go anyway.
Oui. Etje pense qu'on devrait quand même le faire.
No, can't do it. Sorry, Ouinto, you're going back.
Non, impossible. Désolé, Quinto, tu repars.
If you and Leonard get back together, Sheldon and I will finally have...
Si vous vous remettez ensemble, Sheldon et moi aurons enfin
-...someone to go on double dates with. -What about me and Howard?
- un couple avec lequel sortir. - Tu oublies Howard et moi.
Fine, we can double with you too.
Ça peut se faire aussi.
So insecure.
Ce qu'elle est susceptible.
Where are you guys going to eat?
Où comptez-vous manger ?
Penny?
Penny ?
Do you, Penny, take Leonard to be your lawful wedded husband?
Penny, voulez-vous prendre Leonard, ici présent, pour époux ?
Well, it's a little late for me to start saying "no," isn't it?
Ce serait un peu bête de dire ”non" maintenant.
AMY: Penny?
Penny ?
Sorry. ljust remembered I've got to stop by the drugstore.
Pardon. Je Viens de me rappeler que je dois passer àla pharmacie.
[English - US - SDH]
[French]